Thank you for watching.
失意に飲まれ立ち尽くす 麗しき月 Shitsui ni namare tachitsukusu uruwashiku tsuki The beautiful moon stands still in silence
蘇る永遠に彼の光 Yomigaeru tawa ni kare no hikari The eternal light of his light
汚されないて君の胸 Yobosarenaite kimi no dune I was born while praying
祈り合わしながら生まれてきた Inori awa shinagara umarete kita In your dream, I was born while praying
一万年と二千年前から愛してる Ichimannen to nisenenmae kara aishiteru I've loved you for ten thousand years and two thousand years
八千年過ぎた頃からもっと恋しいんだった Hashisennen sugita koro kara motto koishinnatta I've loved you for more than eight thousand years
一億と二千年後も愛してる Ichioku to nisenenmae ato mo aishiteru I've loved you for one hundred million and two thousand years
君を知りたその日から 僕の帰国に 音楽は枯れない Kimi o shiritasu no hi kara boku no kikoku ni ongyaku wa karenai From the day I met you, I can't stop listening to your music
君が繰り返し大人になって Kimi ga kurekai shi otona ni natte You keep becoming an adult
何度も何度も遠くへ行って 見守る僕が眠れない Nando no nando no tooku e itte mimomoru boku ga nemurenai You keep going far away, I can't sleep
僕がクジャクジャになったとしても Boku ga kujakujaninatta to shite no Even if I become a mess
君の名を歌うために Kimi no na o utau tame ni In order to sing your name
一万年と二千年前から愛してる Ichimannen to nisenenmae kara aishiteru I've loved you for ten thousand years and two thousand years
八千年過ぎた頃からもっと恋しくなった Hassen ne sugita koro kara motto koishikunatta I've loved you for more than eight thousand years
一億と二千年後も愛してる Ichiokuto ni sennen ato mo aishiteru I've loved you for ten million and two thousand years
君を知ったその日から Kimi wo shitta sono hi kara I've known you since that day
一万年と二千年前から愛してる Ichimannen to nisenenmae kara aishiteru I've loved you for ten million and two thousand years
八千年過ぎた頃から I've loved you for ten million and two thousand years
八千年過ぎた頃からもっと恋しくなった Kimi wo sugita koro kara motto koishikunatta I've known you for ten million and two thousand years
一億と二千年経っても愛してる Ichiokuto ni sennen tattemo aishiteru I've loved you for ten million and two thousand years
君を知ったその日から Kimi wo shitta sono hi kara I've known you for ten million and two thousand years
僕らの地獄の気温を食わされた Boku no jikoku no kion no kuwakareta I've known you for ten million and two thousand years
たくさん思った通り 今 сам演奏した
Even if I go round and round, I want to be here again
I'll hold your hand so you won't miss me
We talked until the morning sun came back
I can't wait for the sunset to come
Tonight, tomorrow, the day after tomorrow, we'll be together
The light and shadow
In the city where I look at the sunset
I can't find the warmth on my own
I want to see you
I learned that I can be strong
The first time I met you
If I go round and round, I want to be here again
I'll hold your hand so you won't miss me
I can't sleep alone
Because I can't dream
To a place where no anxiety can reach
Let's continue to shine on the starless night
If you and I can go anywhere
We can't walk on our own
If it's just the two of us
I'll walk while singing that song
As long as you're here, I'm happy
Thank you for watching
Thank you.